http://www.telmantec.com/privacy-policy

About Us
Why TTI?
About Us
Why TTI?
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to TELEMANAGEMENT TECHNOLOGIES, INC. (TTI)
This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that TTI collects, and the ways in which TTI uses that personal information.
Personal information collection
Information about your use of this website
Information that you provide for the purpose of registering with the website
Information about transactions carried out over this website
Information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services
Any other information that you send to TTI
Using personal information
TTI may use your personal information to:
Administer this website
Personalize the website for you
Enable your access to and use of the website services
Send to you products that you purchase
Collect payments from you
Send you marketing communications
TTI may disclose your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, TTI may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.
Securing your data
TTI will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
TTI will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.
TTI is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.
Contact TTI
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the treatment of your personal information by TTI, please write to:TeleManagement Technologies, Inc.28202 Cabot Road Suite 300Laguna Niguel, CA 92677Phone: (949)365-5805Fax: (949)315-3458Or by email to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
About TeleManagement Technologies, Inc.
TeleManagement Technologies, Incorporated (TTI) provides Telecom Expense Management and Call Accounting solutions designed to effectively track, integrate, manage and protect an organization's information technology resources. TTI's TEM solution, WinBill®, has developed a reputation for an impressive ROI, with clients reporting savings of 300% or more! WinCall® Call Accounting tracks all domestic and international locations regardless of PBX type (analog, digital, VoIP) to facilitate internal bill back, identify PBX toll fraud and increase employee productivity. Extensive reporting capabilities are also included for planning purposes. TTI's experienced, responsive support team helps keep CFOs and IT/Telecom departments in total control of their technology expenses.Since 1987, TTI has been designing software products that provide a better solution to managing corporate technology, inventory, expenses and services. For more information, visit www.telmantec.com.
We're always happy to assist you with any questions you may have. Just give us a call!
1-800-903-4006
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Inquire by Form
See more options!
Connect with us!
© 2020 TeleManagement Technologies, Inc.
×
Contact Us Today!  Start Saving on Your Technology Spend! 1-800-903-4006
×
newsletter
before content
